if you don't mind I don't know what your next step is to do with it that's why I
don't want to be about tomorrow somebody's gonna tell me you said I said
I'm not here to say I'm not here to I like I told her before we're doing it
this boy find $5 he wants to know what to do with it he can take it to his pocket yeah that's good
I know the ten words I'm really curious because I studied it tonight like I don't religiously you
don't time working you don't have time okay I'm busy well I'm really curious because I
this isn't in the Tanakh so I'm I'm wondering about the ritual the the practice uh what is it you have
to find people you know on AI today you find everything and I don't trust AI there I want
to know don't trust AI because we must put in on AI the right way does that does it is it atonement
the sin transfers to the chicken I'm genuinely asking the sin is transferring to the chicken we hope that
we don't we don't that's also uh debate between people if that's what it does okay the chicken is
you're just saying the chicken is going to die instead of me going to die he's going to die he's
not taking my sins I have to ask God to forgive me for the sins you have to repent yeah so then why is the chicken
necessary
just tell you if you can just repent but repent in case I have to die God wanted me to die let the chicken die instead of me okay but what justifies
the chickens death is it because they have the sins now I don't understand the chickens are getting
that a matter of yes or no because we need to eat chickens well that was my next question does
someone eat these chickens all the chickens are being eaten yeah where does it go where do they go it comes
back in the store to sold to this store to all the stores okay oh it's going back to a place where
there's a lot of chickens but for the people who debate and say that the chickens
- What is this? - What is this?
- It's eating a chicken. - Sir, so if the sins go into the chicken, for those who believe that, then someone eats the sins in the chicken from the meat?
- No, once it gets slaughtered, the sins are gone when it's slaughtered. It's not stuck in the blood?
- There's no blood. You don't need blood. You wash the bloods out.
- How do you get the blood out of the chicken?
- What is this? - What is this?
- You know, we're going to die.
- Sir, you know... - One second.
You need to go pray.
- Did you know Jeremy Yahoo, yeah?
- The prophet?
- Don't wait, come on!
- None?
- Can I ask you just one more genuine?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
- It's a real... I promise it's a genuine question.
- They have more chickens available.
- Do you see people are flying for chickens?
- They want them.
- But the question is...
- Thomas, do you have something else?
- No.
- No more.
- For how did you get the idea?
- Do you have a brain, some Harrison?
- No.
- Okay, so...
- Okay.
- Bye.
- Is this kid now?
- No.
- It was by...
- The kid is made.
- No.
- So you know...
- Jeremiah, the prophet.
- Yeah.
- Chapter 7, verse 22.
- He says, "The day that I brought your fathers out of Egypt, I didn't command them concerning
birth offerings or sacrifices, but this I commanded them: Obey my voice."
- So, if God made sacrifices, how is this necessary?
- After that, they came to the medical, and they...
- To the game of the girl.
- Or even...
- Even Hosea, Hosea 6:6, "I desire mercy, not sacrifice, knowledge of God rather than..."
- The rabbis came, and they said that we should do this.
We follow them.
- But did God, did Hashem say?
- Yes, no, a lot of things, Hashem, there's a lot of things that are...
by the rabbis, a lot of people by Hashem.
In every Shabbat, there's things that we don't do because God said, "Keep the Shabbat."
He didn't say "What?" and "When?" exactly.
And there's things that...
Hey, you need a new motorbike, it looks like.
It's a discussion, you should go to a rabbi and discuss.
- Is it the blood?
Is it the blood that cleanses the sin?
- I have no idea.
I never...
- There's blood itself?
- I know my mother did it.
My father did it.
My grandmother did it.
My great-grandmother in Europe, before World War II, before...
- You don't know why?
- I don't ask.
I come here, my father did it, I did it.
That's how we have to believe.
And that's how this whole community believes.
Whatever my father did, the new generation with AI are skipping it a little bit.
But we hold it up, we follow what we've done.
A lot of people changed their money, but their father didn't do that.
If they had choice, when Hitler was killing people, they didn't have choice, they didn't have chicken, they changed their money.
But it's not because they wanted, but they didn't have a choice.
They were forced.
People now in these days are in some places for the holidays, and they don't have money, I mean a chicken to do it.
They'll take money.
- But if Hashem created a kitchen and gave it life...
- He gave it life.
- He did everything that everybody should have something out of it.
He has cows, he has chickens, he has everything.
- Right.
- What are cows made for?
They make milk.
- Well Genesis...
- Why is the...
- It's God's ideal before sin, right?
- Everything that he made was made for a good purpose that the Jews should enjoy.
- But in Genesis 1:29 it says...
- I don't know, Genesis...
- You don't read Genesis?
- No, I don't know.
- You don't read the Hebrew Bible?
- I have no idea what he talked about.
- Okay.
He doesn't read the Hebrew Bible.
- Well, I don't know what to say about that.
- Joy trip.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
- You're so welcome.